7 hours ago
Why would the Drones just pass by without doing anything?
This doesn't make sense.
This isn't a setup, is it? lol
They said they couldn't read his Psycho-Pass because he was wearing a helmet.
Whooooooooooooooooooa!
Whaaaaaaat? Then the street scanners are pointless!
They said they couldn't read his Psycho-Pass because he was wearing a helmet.
Seriously?
You're kidding!
Whaaaaaaat? Then the street scanners are pointless!
So this is happening for real? That's awful.
Dumbass. This is so obviously fake, lmao
You moron. This isn't real, rofl
This is bad. Seriously, the Area Stress Level must be through the roof.
I'm so scared that I can't go out!
But there's no such thing as murder here, right? lol
I bet you the Bureau's behind this.
Calling the Drones in didn't work, right?
The end of the week is nigh!
I think you mean the end of the world, lol
Helmet, pleaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaase!!
I got a call from my employer.
What did they say?
They said that the area's temporarily closed off, so I shouldn't try to go out.
If we go out, we'll be killed.
What if the Psycho-Pass check at the entrance doesn't work?
But surely the Psycho-Pass check should work, right?
Does this mean that it's dangerous no matter where you are?
Don't even poke your head outside. If they notice you're there, you might end up dead.
If you've got that kind of time on your hands, make a weapon.
Hand over your portable terminals and credit cards.
携帯端末とクレジットカードをよこせ
Give me the passwords too.
パスワードを教えろ
If you see someone wearing a helmet, watch out!
Run! Run! Run! Run! Run! Ruuuuuun!
What do I do?
If their Crime Coefficients can't be measured, there's no point calling the police, right?
Is that friend of yours okay? Isn't he in danger?
I don't know. I can't get through to him.
Someone pls recommend some everyday items that can be used as weapons
You could try swinging a potted houseplant around.
Put something heavy in a sock.
Huh? What's a houseplant?
Stop! Stop it!
やめろ！やめてくれ！
Please stop! I'm begging—
本当に　やめて…
Old-timers like you still stash money under their mattresses, right?
おじいちゃん おばあちゃんって
いまだにタンス預金とかやってるんでしょ？
I saw it on the news.
ニュースで見たよ
Sounds handy. You can just digitize
cash and nobody asks where it's from.
そういうのロンダリングなしで電子化できて 便利だよね
We don't have anything like that in this house.
そんなもの… ないよ この家には…
I would like to show
Cut open my skull
Look into my head
I don't know why I'm so harsh
I could be so brash
I'm going to clash
'Cause I feel
I can always show my everything to you
If this moment was for me
I try to hear, lend my ear
Voices inside
One link to join it all again
'Cause I feel
I can always show my everything to you
If this moment was for me
I try to hear, lend my ear
Voices inside
One link to join it all
So it goes again
#15: The Town Where Sulfur Falls
本字幕由诸神字幕组制作 更多字幕欢迎访问http://www.kamigami.org
翻译:草泥马 知音   校对:西西   时间轴:葛蔓 压制：娜夏
And thus, today we've brought together all
you top honor students from the same school.
という訳で今日は同期でもトップクラスの優等生諸君に
Greetings, ladies and gentlemen.
集まっていただきました
Don't you guys think it's totally unfair?
めちゃくちゃ不公平だと思いません？
I mean, you all have promising futures.
前途有望な君たち
But we know before we even try that we'll never amount to anything.
それに対してやる前から何もかも駄目だって分かってる俺たち
Why are you doing this?
何でこんな…
Stop it! This is terrible!
やめて…ひどい…
This is nothing compared to the Sibyl System's cruelty.
ひどいのは俺たちじゃなくてシビュラシステムだよ
Sibyl's Judgment has robbed us of
any chance we had for a good career.
シビュラの判定で
俺たちはもうろくな仕事に就けないことは分かってる
We live with no hope for the future.
将来に何の期待もない人生なんてさ
But since you've all enjoyed Sibyl's
blessing, you wouldn't understand, would you?
システムに祝福されてるお前らには分かんないだろ
What the hell's your problem?!
何なんだよもう
We saw you take one of those helmets off earlier.
さっき　あんたがヘルメット脱ぐのを見たんだよ
Huh?
So after causing all that mayhem, you thought
you could just take the helmet off and play dumb.
散々暴れておいて ヘルメットを脱いだだけで知らんぷり決め込もうとは
That's screwed up, man.
ちょっとひどいんじゃないか
You've got the wrong guy!
勘違いしてる　あんたら
If you really think I did all that, why don't you check my Hu—
そういうなら俺の色相を…
You helmet-wearing bastards are raising the
Area Stress level of the whole neighborhood.
お前らヘルメットのせいで エリアストレスが上昇してるんだ
Whatever you do, just leave us the hell out of it!
頼むから巻き込まないでくれよ
This won't raise our Crime Coefficients, will it?
私たちの犯罪係数が上がったりしませんよね
I read on the 'net before that if you
fight in self-defense or attack criminals,
さっきネットで見ました
正当防衛だったり
相手が犯罪者なら むしろ犯罪係数は下降するそうです
it actually reduces your Crime Coefficient instead.
It's chaos outside.
Call the Public Safety Bureau!
What is the Bureau doing?!
Stay inside and hide.
Call the Public Safety Bureau!
What is the Bureau doing?!
Stay inside and hide.
I didn't manage to escape...
So what happens when totally unrelated people get dragged into this?
What is the Bureau doing?!
Stay inside and hide.
I didn't manage to escape...
So what happens when totally unrelated people get dragged into this?
Eh. They're trash who won't contribute anything to society anyway.
Aren't there latent criminals in there as well?
I bet all of your Hues have gotten clouded already.
The guys in helmets aren't the only criminals.
It's too late.
If those helmet people are killed, things'll be peaceful again, right?
Self defense. Self-defense. Self-defense...
No, no, no, no, no...
Come on, listen to yourselves!
It's not too late. We need to take matters into our own hands.
Isn't that dangerous?
Several dozen cases...
It's better than doing nothing.
数十件…
No, several hundred cases!
いや　数百件 まだ増えてる
The number keeps growing!
The brutality is spreading like a contagion.
凶暴性の伝染
Has the Psycho-Hazard grown by this much?
サイコハザードがここまで大規模に…
It's more than that.
そんなお上品なもんじゃない
At this point, it's become a full-blown riot.
ここまでくりゃ暴動だ
The Area Stress Level is rising like crazy too.
エリアストレス上昇もえらいことになってる
It's not just the helmet-wearers who've gone on a rampage.
Aren't they just latent criminals from the start?
暴れてるのはヘルメットの連中だけじゃない
Scared citizens are committing
widespread acts of violence all over the place.
おびえた市民があっちこっちで集団暴行を引き起こしている
Must be a Psycho-Hazard...
It's begun...
Someone without a helmet on is going on a rampage?!
Run! Run! Run! Run! Run! Ruuuuuuun!
Chief Kasei issued an emergency summons.
禾生局長より緊急招集だ
She's ordering all CID personnel to report for duty, including those who are off duty.
非番の人員も含め 刑事課に総動員指令が下った
You sound restless.
落ち着かないかね
Yeah, of course. This situation would make anyone uneasy.
そりゃね
不安にもなりますよ
What's awaiting us from here on out?
果たしてここから先に何が待っているのか
What will happen to this town?
この街がどうなってしまうのか
I really like that ordinary side of yours.
君のそういう普通なところ すごくいいと思う
You and I are both quite ordinary, essentially common people.
僕も君も　ごく普通で本質的にありきたりな人間だ
I've never thought of myself as avaricious.
自分のことを欲張りだと思ったことはないよ
I just long for a world in which
everyday things are done in an everyday way.
当たり前のことが 当たり前に行われる世界
That's all I really want.
僕は そういうのが好きなだけでね
Here we are, two ordinary, unremarkable people...
ごく普通でありきたりなわれわれが 普通でない街に犯罪を仕掛ける
instigating crime in a town that isn't ordinary at all.
A town that isn't ordinary, huh?
「普通でない街」か…
How should I put it...
何だろうな…
This town is like a parody of one of the old novels I used to read.
昔読んだ小説のパロディーみたいだ　この街は…
Like the ones by William Gibson?
例えば…ウィリアム·ギブスンですか
More like Philip K. Dick, perhaps.
フィリップ·Ｋ·ディックかな
It's not as controlling as the society George Orwell
depicted, and it's not as wild as what Gibson depicted.
ジョージ·オーウェルが描く社会ほど支配的でなく
ギブスンが描くほどワイルドでもない
I've never read Dick.
ディック 読んだことないな…
Which book would you recommend I read first?
最初に１冊読むなら何がいいでしょう
"Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?"
『アンドロイドは電気羊の夢を見るか？』
They based an old movie on that story, didn't they?
古い映画の原作ですね
Yes, though the original is quite different.
だいぶ内容が違う
You should compare them when you have time someday.
いつか暇なときに比較してみるといい
I'll go ahead and download it.
ダウンロードしておきます
Why don't you buy paper books?
紙の本を買いなよ 電子書籍は味気ない
E-books lack character.
Is that right?
そういうもんですかね
Books aren't just something you read.
本はね ただ文字を読むんじゃない
They're like a form of meditation.
自分の感覚を調整するためのツールでもある
Meditation?
調整？
Sometimes, when I'm not feeling well,
I read books but I don't really absorb them.
調子の悪いときに本の内容が頭に入ってこないことがある
When that happens, it makes me think
about what could be getting in the way.
そういうときは何が読書の邪魔をしているか考える
There are also books that I can absorb even when I'm feeling down.
調子が悪いときでも　すらすらと内容が入ってくる本もある
Sometimes I wonder why.
なぜそうなのか考える
It could be like mental conditioning.
精神的な調律 チューニングみたいなものかな
I think it's all about the stimulation your brain receives when you turn the pages.
調律する際大事なのは
紙に指で触れている感覚や
The feeling of flipping them over, one by one.
本をぺらぺらめくったとき 瞬間的に脳の神経を刺激するものだ
That's kind of a downer.
何だかへこむな…
Hm?
When I talk with you, I feel like I've
been missing out on something all my life.
あなたと話していると
俺の今までの人生　ずっと損をしてたような気分になる
You're reading too much into it.
考え過ぎだね
Maybe.
ですかね
It's about time.
そろそろ時間だ
Shall we go?
行きますか
This is just a random thought, but...
どうでもいいんだけどさ
Yeah?
It's just too perfect that such an
outstanding hacker would be into Gibson.
はい？
すご腕のハッカーがギブスン好きってのは でき過ぎだな
We're currently facing an unprecedented crisis all across the metropolitan area.
目下　首都圏は未曽有の危機に直面している
When the Sibyl System was introduced, people believed
it would eliminate all possibility of a riot among the citizens.
シビュラシステムの導入以来
市民の暴動は　可能性として廃絶されたものと判断されたため
Therefore, the current Public Safety Bureau has neither
the personnel nor the equipment to suppress such a mob.
現在の公安局には　暴徒の鎮圧に備えた人員も装備もない
We've been at peace for too long.
あまりにも平和が長過ぎた
We're currently trying to bring in the border
security Drones and equip them with non-lethal weapons,
現在国境警備ドローンの装備を
非殺傷兵器に換装する作業が急ピッチで進められているが
but the situation out there requires prompt action.
現場の状況は一刻を争う
Until a full-fledged suppression unit is formed,
本格的な鎮圧部隊の編成が整うまでの間
we have no choice but to have those of you at the CID
act as the last remaining shield to keep our citizens safe.
諸君ら刑事課のメンバーに
市民の安全を守る最後の盾となってもらうしかない
The cymatic scan-proof helmets we have
observed hinder the functionality of the Dominators.
問題のサイマティックスキャン妨害ヘルメットは
ドミネーターの機能を阻害する
Stun batons are therefore our most
effective weapon for dealing with the rioters.
これに対して最も有効なスタンバトンで対処してもらう
I'll also permit the use of electromagnetic
pulse grenades for crowd control in emergencies.
相手が大人数の場合は
緊急用の電磁パルスグレネードの使用を許可する
Once the helmet's electronics are knocked out by the
EMP, you'll be able to use your Dominators in the usual way.
サージ電流によりヘルメットが無力化されれば
従来どおりドミネーターによる執行が可能になる
However, make sure you pay careful
attention to when you use the grenades.
ただし グレネードの使用についてはくれぐれも慎重に配慮すること
If you let off an EMP in the wrong location, you might disable vital city facilities as well.
うかつな場所で電磁パルスを発生させれば
都市機能のまひもあり得る
How many grenades do we have?
グレネードの数はどれくらいでしょう
Not many.
多くはない
Probably enough to give out two to each person here.
ここにいる全員に１人２個ずつで品切れだろう
You'll form teams of three.
３人で１チームつくってもらう
Each team is to take an area and
suppress the riots there one by one.
そしてエリアを分担してあとはしらみつぶしで鎮圧だ
It'll be time-consuming and dangerous, but we don't have any other choice.
時間がかかるし　危険も伴うが
他に方法はない
The whole town's future is at stake.
この街の未来が懸かっている
I'm counting on all of you.
よろしく頼む
I always knew you and I would be
traveling down a dangerous road together.
あなたと一緒に歩くのが危ない橋だって自覚はあった
But you never wanted to turn back.
でも　引き返す気にはなれなかった
Well, don't you think it's strange?
だって変ですもん シビュラシステムって
The Sibyl System.
All those people who are happy entrusting everything in their
lives to some nonsense like that? They're the ones who are crazy.
あんな訳の分かんないものに生活の全てを預けて
平気な連中の方がどうかしている
I'm a foreigner, you know. I appreciate
simply being able to live in this country.
俺は外国人ですからね
この国で暮らしていけるだけでも感謝 と言いたいところなんですが
Well, that's what I'd like to say,
but in the end it's just like you said, Makishima.
槙島さんの言ったとおりですよ
I also desire a world where we can just do everyday things in an everyday way.
当たり前のことを当たり前にできるように…
This is my hometown. It's where I was born and raised.
僕にとっては生まれ育った街だ
I want to put things right as soon as possible.
切実な問題だよ
These guys want to see what lies beyond the destruction you'll cause.
こいつらはあなたが行う破壊の先を見たがっている連中です
Beyond the destruction, huh?
「破壊の先」か…
Well, if that happens, more the better.
先があればよし
But I don't mind if this is the end.
なければ それはそれで受け入れる
How are you going with manipulating information on the 'net?
ネットでの情報操作は
The AI I set up beforehand is already at work.
事前に仕掛けたＡＩがもう活動中です
Makishima Shougo... He's really done it this time.
やってくれるぜ　槙島聖護
Hold on a sec, though.
でも　待ってください
We still haven't found conclusive evidence that
Makishima has anything to do with these helmet incidents.
このヘルメット犯罪に槙島が関与しているという決定的な証拠は
まだ見つかっていません
Think about it.
考えてみろ　普通の人間は
The moment an ordinary person even thinks of making
something that'd undermine the Sibyl System, it shows in their Hue.
シビュラシステムを無効化する装備を作ってみようと思った時点で
色相が濁る
But whoever was behind the helmet
designed it, mass produced it, and distributed it.
それを設計し 量産し ばらまいた
The whole process probably took a few months at least.
下準備には数カ月はかかっているだろう
He'd have to order parts, arrange distribution and so on.
部品の発注　流通の手配
There's no way he'd be able to do that
while avoiding all the scanners around town.
街じゅうのスキャナーを避けながらできることじゃない
The only person who could make that helmet
あのヘルメットを作れるのは
is someone who could defeat the
Sibyl System without needing one himself.
ヘルメットなしにシビュラシステムに対抗できる人間だけだ
So he took advantage of a blind spot in the
Sibyl System to engineer a mass Psycho-Hazard?
シビュラシステムの盲点を突いた
集団サイコハザード
That was Makishima's goal?
それが槙島の目的ってこと
No.
違う…
What?
Makishima's crimes always had a purpose
behind them. He was always looking for answers.
だって　槙島の犯罪は
いつだって何か答えを探すようなところがあった
This is a truly fearsome riot, but I can't
believe that this chaos could be his only goal.
ひどい暴動だけど
この混乱だけが目的とは思えない
I agree with you, Inspector.
監視官に賛成だ
If all he wanted to do was watch the city burn, he'd be a lot easier for us to apprehend.
こんな暴動を見物して喜ぶ程度の犯罪者だったなら
もっと楽に逮捕できる
Ouch. Things are looking bad online too.
ネット上もひどいな
There's a mishmash of false rumors
and real information flying back and forth.
デマからマブネタまで大量に飛び交ってる
I thought we were keeping a lid on media coverage?
報道規制はかかってるはずなのに…
Made-up rumors attract more attention anyway.
デマの方が目立つな
What the hell?
何だよ
"The Bureau's killing all the townspeople"?!
「公安局が住民皆殺し」って
We have to stop them!
止めなきゃ
Why don't you just run them over with the car?
このまま突っ込んで何人かひき殺しちゃいなよ
No way!
やですよ
Well, I thought it was a good idea.
俺グッドアイデアだと思ったけど
In what way?!
どこがですか
This is the Public Safety Bureau!
厚生省公安局です
Stop this violence immediately and lay
down with your hands behind your head!
直ちに暴力行為をやめて
腕を頭の上で組んで地面に伏せなさい
We have no choice but to resort to force.
実力行使しかないな
Give them another warning!
もう一度警告だ
This is the Public Safety Bureau!
こちらは厚生省公安局です
Cease this violence immediately or we'll be forced to use Dominators!
これ以上暴力行為を停止しない場合は
ドミネーターを使用します
We will not hesitate to use lethal force on those of you with high Crime Coefficients!
犯罪係数によっては命を失うことになります
I repeat! Lay down with your hands behind your head!
繰り返します
腕を頭の上で組んで地面に伏せなさい
Why are you doing this?!
何だよ　悪いのはヘルメットの連中じゃないか
The guys in helmets are the real criminals!
What's the Bureau going to do about
all the helmets that are already out there?
公安局は大量に出回ってるヘルメットの方を何とかしろよ
We're the victims, aren't we?!
俺たちは被害者だろ
Shut up! You're breaking the law too!
うるせえな
それはそれ　これはこれ
What's the matter?
どうしたんですか
These guys are victims as well.
こいつらも被害者だ
Yeah.
確かに 犯罪に巻き込まれなければ 市民の暴徒化なんて…
If the citizens hadn't been dragged into
this, they wouldn't have become so violent.
No. I mean the helmet-wearers.
違う　ヘルメットの方だ
It might take time, but eventually they'll all
be hunted down and killed, just like this lot.
今やったように 時間はかかるが
いずれヘルメット着用者は全員狩り殺される
And the ones we don't catch will be killed by gangs of citizens.
俺たちがやらなくても市民がリンチにかける
Something's been bothering me.
さっきちょっと気になったんだ
The false rumors on the 'net are getting worse and worse.
ネット上のデマが攻撃的な方向に偏っている
What if this is another case of Makishima
manipulating information for his own purposes?
これが槙島の情報操作の一環だとしたら…
We already know that either he or one of
his accomplices is an accomplished hacker.
やつ自身か それともやつの仲間か…
どちらかがすご腕のクラッカーなのはもう分かってる
Otherwise, all those crimes wouldn't have been possible.
そうじゃなきゃできない犯罪ばかりだった
Look at all those people who
surrendered and took off their helmets.
今投降してヘルメットを脱いだ連中の顔を見てみろよ
They're scum who'd never be able to commit crimes otherwise.
ヘルメットがなけりゃ何の犯罪もできないクズどもだ
In a sense, they're all just Makishima's pawns.
ある意味　槙島の手のひらの上で踊っていただけさ
Hold on a sec.
ちょい待ち ってことは　槙島の狙いは…
If that's the case, then what is Makishima's goal?
Let's suppose that everything is going according to his plan.
全てがやつの筋書きどおりだったと仮定する
Maybe he even anticipated what we'd do at this very moment.
今俺たちがやってることさえやつの思うつぼだとしたら…
Inspector, which riot locations were we asked to suppress first?
監視官　まず優先対象として鎮圧要請のあった暴動箇所は
Let's see...
えっと…
Here they are.
ここです
I think he's been playing us from the start.
考えられるのは陽動だ
What if the whole thing was set up so that the riots would flare up
これが全て刑事課の人員をおびき寄せるためだけに
in such a way that all the CID's detectives would be lured out?
あらかじめ暴動が激化するように仕組まれたポイントだとしたら…
You don't mean... No way!
これは…まさか
I've spent these last five years
desperately trying to figure out the Sibyl System.
この５年間
俺はシビュラシステムの実態をつかむために 血眼になってきました
"Distributed parallel processing by servers
installed throughout the metropolitan area."
首都圏各地に設置されたサーバーによる分散型並列処理
"A model system that makes iron-clad fault tolerance a reality."
鉄壁のフォールトトレラントを実現した理想のシステム
Those are the catchphrases used by the Ministry of Welfare.
それが厚生省のうたい文句です
Of course, analyzing and measuring the
Psycho-Pass of every citizen in this country
まあ実際 全国民のサイコパスを測定し分析するともなれば
requires a great deal of computing power.
膨大な演算が必要になる
As you might imagine, such computational feats are
impossible without distributed computing over a series of nodes.
当然　ネットワークを経由したグリッドコンピューティングい
でもしないかぎり追い付かな
However, the more I looked into it, the more I realized
ところがね　検証すればするほど
that something about the flow of data made no sense.
データの流れ方が明らかにおかしい
Scanners throughout town, authorized
counseling AIs, the Dominators, and so on...
街じゅうのスキャナー  公認カウンセリングＡＩ
そして　ドミネーター
At first glance, it looked like the data was just being distributed throughout the grid,
一見グリッドを巡り巡っているかのように見えたデータが
but it was actually just being passed from one place to another.
実は全てたらい回しにされてるだけだった
Then, I finally noticed it.
そこでようやく気付いたんです
There's a single relay point that every piece
of data transmitted through the Sibyl System
シビュラを巡る全ての通信が必ず一度は経由する中継点が
passes through at least once, without exception.
ただ１カ所だけ存在することに
If we consider the possibility that
there is a stand-alone system hidden there
もしそこに誰も知らないスタンドアローンのシステムが隠されてて
that is responsible for all of Sibyl's processing and computation,
全てのシビュラの処理演算をそいつ１機が賄っているのだとしたら…
everything makes sense.
全て辻褄が合うんです
You really are a genius.
やはり君は天才だね
What's strange, though, is its capacity.
まあ不可解なのはその性能ですよ
If everything really is handled by this one system,
もし孤立したシステムだとすると
the sheer throughput it must have is beyond
what should be possible with current technology.
そいつは既存の技術では説明のつかないスループットを発揮していることになる
As well as that, it makes no sense
to put it all in one place to begin with.
そもそも１カ所に集約している意味が分からない
It's far too great of a security risk no matter how you look at it.
保安上のリスクを考えればどう考えても危険過ぎる
Maybe they just want to keep it secret at all costs.
あるいはあえて危険を冒してまで 秘匿性を保ちたいのだとしたら
Exactly.
そういうこと
But when I discover something that fishy, I can't help but sniff around.
ここまでうさんくさいとなるとね
もう確かめなきゃ気が済まなくなりますよ
I had to find out the truth behind the Sibyl System.
シビュラシステムの正体ってやつを…
And you tracked it back to this facility?
そして 君が確かめた問題の施設がここか
This is the relay point at which all the cymatic scan data intersects.
サイマティックスキャンで収集されたあらゆるデータの中継点
There are also clear signs that the true power consumption in this area has been concealed.
おまけにこのエリアの消費電力 明らかに偽装されてる形跡があります
I'm almost certain that the Sibyl System resides
within this building: the Ministry of Welfare's Nona Tower.
ほぼ間違いなくシビュラシステムはこの厚生省ノナタワーの中にある
Well, then...
さあ　それでは諸君
why don't we all uncover the heart of the Great Prophetess?
ひとつ暴き出してやろうじゃないか
偉大なる神託の巫女のはらわたを…
Inspector Ginoza!
宜野座さん　首謀者の目的は厚生省ノナタワーの襲撃です
The man behind these incidents is planning
to attack the Ministry of Welfare's Nona Tower!
The riots are just a diversion!
暴動は全ておとりなんです
Don't be ridiculous!
You are not to leave your post based on groundless speculation!
バカな そんな根拠のない臆測で持ち場を離れるな
People's lives are at stake!
こっちは人命が懸かってるんだぞ
But since all the Inspectors and Enforcers are out on
the field, the government district in the Chuo Ward is empty!
でも　監視官も執行官も全て出払った中央区の官庁街はもぬけの殻ですよ
The guard Drones might as well be scarecrows to these guys!
あいつらの手に掛かったら
警備ドローンなんてカカシも同然です
If we stay here and let them carry out their
plan, we won't get a second chance to stop them!
このまま後手に回っていたら
今度こそ取り返しのつかない事態になります
Please let us go, if only us!
せめて　私たちだけでも
Okay!
分かった
You guys go there first and find out what's happening!
まずは君たちが先行して状況を確認しろ
We'll continue to suppress the riots in each area.
こちらは引き続き各地の鎮圧を続行する
If anything happens, let me know immediately!
何かあったら　すぐ　連絡を
Okay!
はい
Here it is!
見えてきたぜ
There's no way I could love anyone,
Dareka wo aisuru koto nante
Dekiru wake nakutte
But I wish to be loved by someone in turn
The world may not have
Dakedo dareka ni aisaretakute
Ended yesterday after all,
Kawaranai kinou ga zutto tsuzuita to shite mo
But we will not budge
Doko ni mo ike ya shinainda
watashi to kimi
From where we are
Kamisama doko he itte shimatta no nee
God, in favor of which parts have you left us?
Henji wa nakute itsu datte sou da yo
I receive no reply, I never do
Are you still here?
You'll never walk alone
I walk with you
Anata to iku
Donna tsumi mo
I will share all your sins
Seotte ageru
Together with you
Michi naki michi wo
Aruiteku no
I walk
A trackless path
Anata to futari de
This story is a work of fiction. The names of all individuals and organizations that appear
in this show are fictitious and any similarity to those in existence in the real world is purely coincidental.
This is a world where the mental state and
personal tendencies of humans can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed,
these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are
commonly called "Psycho-Pass".
This is a world where the mental state and
personal tendencies of humans can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed,
these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are
commonly called "Psycho-Pass".